[Peter] This one was a little tricky, but you should get it if you understand assignment.
这个问题有点棘手 但是如果你了解赋值语句 应该就没有问题
The answers are all of them except this one,
答案是除了这一个 其他都正确
and we'll go over each one one by one.
我们一个一个说明
I've initialized their values to represent colors,
我用颜色来表示它们初始化的值
but they can be any integer as described in the question.
但是如问题所述 它们可以是任意整数
The first line of code states that a refers to what x refers to,
第一行代码说 a 指向 x 所指向的值
so let's change that.
因此 让我们来改变它
The second says that a now refers to what a refers to
第二行说 a 指向原来 a 指向的值加 1
plus 1, so now a refers to a new number,
所以现在指向一个新数字
which is the red triangle plus 1.
也就是红色三角形加 1
At the end of these 2 statements, x still equals
在这两个赋值结束后
what it was originally, and that is the red triangle.
x 仍然等于它原来的值 红色三角形
A and x as described refer to initial values.
a 和 x 指向初始值
The first line of code says that a refers to what x refers to,
代码的第一行说 a 指向 x 所指向的值
so as we did in the last problem, we result in that a and x
如同上一个问题 导致 a 和 x
both refer to the red triangle.
指向红色三角形
Now x refers to what a refers to.
现在 x 指向 a 所指向的值
Well, as you can see, a also refers to the red triangle,
嗯 如你所见 a 也指向红色三角形
so the result of this is that x still refers to the red triangle,
所以结果是  x 仍然指向红色三角形
and since that's what it was initially, the value of x has not yet changed.
因为 x 值和初始值一样 并未改变
In this choice, the value of x changes.
在这个选项 x 的值改变了
Let's show you why.
让我们来告诉你为什么
The first line of code says that x now refers to what it used to refer to plus 1,
代码的第一行说 x 指向 x 原来指向的值加 1
so we're going to create a new value that is the red triangle plus 1
因此 我们要创造一个新值 红色三角形加 1
and change what x points to.
并且改变 x 指向的值
The second line says x should now refer to what x refers to.
第二行说 x 应该指向 x 所指向的值
Well, it doesn't change what it's referring to now,
嗯 它并没有改变指向的值
which is the red triangle plus 1.
仍是红色三角形加 1
The end result is that x does not refer to the red triangle any longer,
最后结果是  x 不再指向红色三角形
which is why it's not the correct choice.
也就是说它不是正确的选项
The forth choice may be a little bit of Python that you haven't seen before.
第四个选项可能是你从未见过的 Python 语句
What this says is a should equal x,
它说 a 应该等于 x
and x should equal a.
x 应该等于 a
The end result is that x and a swap.
最后结果是  x 和 a 作交换 (swap)
Let's see what that looks like,
让我们看看是怎么回事
and I'll draw this all the way around here.
我把线画到这里来
X and a have swapped values.
x 和 a 交换了值
X now refers to the green triangle, and a the red triangle.
x 现在指向绿色三角形 a 指向红色三角形
The second line of code is exactly the same as the first.
代码的第二行和第一行是完全一样的
It's going to swap them again,
两者又交换一次
and if you swap 2 things twice,
如果你将两个东西交换两次
you get what you had before,
会得到你原有的东西
so since x refers to the red triangle still,
既然 x 指向红色三角形
it's a correct choice.
这是一个正确的选项
In the last choice, we have a third variable x, a, z.
最后的选项 我们有了第三个变量 x、a、z
We initialize z to the value of x,
我们将 z 初始化为 x 的值
which is the red triangle.
是红色三角形
We then assign a to what z refers to,
然后 我们将 a 指定为 z 所指向的值
which is also the red triangle.
也是红色三角形
And lastly, we set x to the value of a.
最后 我们将 x 设为 a 的值
A refers to the red triangle, so x also refers to the red triangle.
a 指向红色三角形 所以 x 也指向红色三角形
The end result is the value of x hasn't changed.
最后结果是  x 的值并没有改变